English

English

English

|     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
|     | [Downloads](https://www.freemake.com/downloads/) |     | [Support](https://www.freemake.com/support/) |     | [How to](https://www.freemake.com/how_to/) |     | Help us |     |     |

Privacy Statement
=================

Introduction
------------

We at Freemake are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. Freemake has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information. For the purposes of this statement, "Personal Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home.

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Freemake website [www.freemake.com](https://www.freemake.com/2/)

Information Collection
----------------------

Freemake doesn’t collect any kind of personal information when you use our applications.

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you want to provide us with your personal data, to give us the opportunity to get in touch with you.

If you choose to create an account on Help Desk to contact the Freemake Support Team, you enter your email address, name, and surname, password, location. This data is not listed publicly. It is saved within the Help Desk program and is used by the technical support only to get in touch with you.

When you enter a contest or other promotional event, we may ask for information such as your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.

We use Google Analytics (https://www.google.com/analytics) to track our website traffic. It is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic.

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your time spent at our sites, and to gather broad demographic information. This allows us to see which parts of our site users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means, for instance, that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will remain anonymous. We do not use this information for any other purposes.

When a user submits personal information, it is kept on a private server not accessible from the Internet. This limits the possibility of any malicious use of your information.

Credit Card Purchase: Freemake doesn't process credit card data itself. All payments are accepted through the payment service providers https://fastspring.com/ and https://www.paypal.com. Information about your credit card is not kept in or recorded by Freemake, it is simply passed through to the credit card company. In this respect, credit card purchase on the internet is like a credit card purchase at any store.

Such information as email address, name, and surname, transaction ID, a serial number are kept by Freemake or further delivery and/or registration of the product.

Use of personal information
---------------------------

Freemake software does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Freemake behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against Freemake policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent. In short, Freemake does not sell registrant information to lists. In some cases, Freemake may use a visitor's personal information to understand overall patterns for site usage, to contact the user for clarification on inaccurate information, or to follow up on a customer service issue. Personal information may include name, address, telephone number, etc.

Links to other sites
--------------------

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Freemake is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web Sites as well as any information they might collect, even though our name or logo may appear on those sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the Privacy Statements of each and every Web site that you visit, as the privacy policy of those sites may differ from ours. Our Privacy Statement applies solely to [www.freemake.com](https://www.freemake.com/2/)

Third-party ads
---------------

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp/)

We may use [third-party advertising companies](https://d1yfi78xmq69ay.cloudfront.net/pp.html) to serve ads when you visit our website.

About the use of cookies and personal data
------------------------------------------

This website uses cookies and similar technologies that store information on your PC, mobile phone or tablet. This is usually stored on the device's browser. We use cookies to grant visitors’ access to different functions on our websites, differentiate the users from each other, and analyze our website's performance and to utilize user-adapted interest-based advertising. This relies to some degree on the use of personally identifiable information from our users – as described below – and helps us improve our website and make our digital communication more relevant for our recipients.

Our visitors can voluntarily choose to accept the use of cookies through the settings on your browser or device. In your browser settings, you can adjust the preferences of which cookies your browser downloads. There, you can also delete all existing cookies that are stored on your browser or device. Please advise that if you block all cookies on your browser or device, this can result in a drop in our (and others) website performance and functions.

### Purpose of cookies on this website

Our website uses cookies placed either by us or by third parties for the following purposes:

* **Analysis:** We utilize cookies to count unique visitors on our websites and to develop statistics regarding our websites operations and functionality. The software we utilize stores information about page impressions served and user information regarding geographical location, device, operating system and browser.
* **Log in services:** If the webpage has the possibility for log in services, we store an ID number and time of log in on a cookie on your browser or device. This enables that you do not have to log in again after each page you open.
* **Interest-based advertising online:** You can experience to see advertisements this website on other websites due to the cookies placed on your browser or device. We base this information most frequently on consumed content, user information or geographical location. Through this method, we try to identify your interests and make our advertisements more relevant for you. This is a remarketing technology and is a product delivered from third party suppliers such as Google or Facebook.
* **Twin profiles:** We base the creation of twin profiles on behavioral data collected from our websites. In account of the knowledge we have on one cluster of users, we extend these users to new segments that have the similar interest and behavior as the original cluster of users.

If you wish to know more details regarding the use of cookies that are on this website, how we use them, third party access and which information we store please open the link **“List of cookies and their adjoining third party supplier”** further down on this page. Since some of our third-party suppliers also can use our cookies for information, you can find their contact information further down on this page.

### Contact – Inquiry of access

Please send an email to [emma.cooper@freemake.com](mailto:emma.cooper@freemake.com) if you want access to, extradite, correct or delete personal data that we have stored about you. You can also protest, demand limitations or withdraw your consent(s) at any time.

### List of cookies and their adjoining third party supplier

\*You can read about purpose of cookies on this website under the link **“Purpose of cookies on this website”** above.

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Name** | **\*Purpose** | **Timeframe** | **Third party access and  <br>contact information** |
| Google Analytics | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | https://www.google.com/analytics/ |
| Facebook | Interest based marketing | Maximum 540 days | facebook.com, staticxx.facebook.com |
| Twitter | Interest based marketing | Maximum 540 days | twitter.com, platform.twitter.com |
| Yandex | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | yandex.ru, mc.yandex.ru |
| Google+ | Interest based marketing | Maximum 540 days | apis.google.com,accounts.google.com |
| Paypal | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | paypalobjects.com |
| DoubleClick | Analysis | Maximum 30 days | doubleclick.net |
| Stumbleupon | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | badge.stumbleupon.com |
| Youtube | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | youtube.com |
| Hatena | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | b.hatena.ne.jp, hatena.ne.jp |
| Dotomi | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | vcm-match.dotomi.com, dotomi.com |
| Content.ad | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | api.content-ad.com |
| Conversant LLC | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | fastclick.net |
| Skimlinks | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | skimresources.com |
| Adobe | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | dpm.demdex.net, demdex.net |
| Oracle | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | bluekai.com |
| content.ad | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | content.ad |
| Cloudflare | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | cloudflare.com |
| Vkontakte | Interest based marketing | Maximum 540 days | vk.com |
| Apple | Analysis | Maximum 540 days | apple.com |

Children's Privacy
------------------

Freemake website is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.

YouTube API Services
--------------------

We use YouTube API Services in consistence with YouTube [Terms of Service](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms) (ToS) and [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

Your Consent
------------

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Freemake's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please [contact us](mailto:freemake@freemake.com). While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
|     | © 2010-2024 Mixbyte Inc.<br><br>Privacy policy<br><br>Terms of use<br><br>DMCA<br><br>GDPR<br><br>[About](https://www.freemake.com/about_us/) |     |
